我可以显示像素的值，而不仅仅显示各个像素的值
Instead of just displaying values of individual pixels I can display the values of the pixels
沿着场景中的一条线。我们来看看这个。
along a line in the scene. Let’s have a look at this.
要做到这一点，我在这里使用线路按钮，我点击这里的第一点，我要去
To do that I use the line button here and I click the first point here and I am going
单击此处的第二个点。在原始图像和另一个图像上绘制一条线
to click a second point over here. Draws a line on the original image and in the other
窗口我们看到我们称之为强度轮廓。所以我们可以看到强度是最初的
window we see what we call an intensity profile. So we can see that the intensity is initially
非常明亮-我们在墙上-然后当我们向右移动时
quite bright—we’re on the wall—then as we move further towards the right along
那条线强度下降，在门口变得很暗。如果你走出了
that line the intensity drops, gets quite dark in the doorway. If you come out of the
门口再次穿过一段墙，像素值得到了很大的价值，它
doorway and cross a section of wall again the pixel values have got a large value, it
是一堵明亮的墙，然后当我们经历下一个时，它们会下降到较低的值
is a bright wall, and then they fall down to a lower value as we go through the next
窗口。所以，这是像素值的模式
window. So, this is the pattern of pixel values as
我们沿着原始场景中的一条线移动。我们可以做的另一件事是创造什么
we move along a line within the original scene. Another thing we can do is to create what
被称为感兴趣的区域，有效地放大到其中的矩形区域
is called a region of interest, effectively to zoom in onto a rectangular region within
图片。那么让我们来看看。我将做的是删除此个人资料
the image. So let’s have a look at that. What I will do is I will remove this profile
图像，我将点击缩放按钮，我将以交互方式套接图像的一个区域
image and I will click the zoom button, and I will lasso an area of the image interactively
结果是一个较小的图像，其中包含原始图像的子区域。
and the result is a smaller image which contains a sub region of the original image.